pricespider.com 2007-06-23

# PriceSpider :: Privacy & Security

|  |   
---  
| **Privacy & Security** |   
---|---  
|  **PRICESPIDER PRIVACY POLICY**  
---  
Updated: July 11, 2005   
**INTRODUCTION**  
PriceSpider is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement explains data collection and use practices of the PriceSpider site. By accessing PriceSpider.com, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy statement. 

Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor sites, have their own privacy statements which can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective web site.   
  
**COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
PriceSpider.com does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, we may collect certain information about your visit, such as the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the PriceSpider.com, the pages that you access while at PriceSpider.com and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. This information is used to help improve the site, analyze trends and administer the site.   
**USE OF COOKIES**  
PriceSpider may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of delivering relevant content, eases site navigation, and so on. When you return to the Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the sites features that you customized. 

We may occasionally opt to share aggregated site statistics with partner companies, but do not allow other companies to place cookies on our site unless there is a temporary, overriding customer value (such as merging into PriceSpider.com a site that relies on third-party cookies). 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this or other Web sites you visit.   
  
**USE OF WEB BEACONS**  
PriceSpider.com Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons sometimes also called single-pixel gifs that allow PriceSpider to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. PriceSpider may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. 

Some of these Web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or email communications. These Web beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer. Doing this allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views. PriceSpider prohibits Web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information.   
  
**PARTICIPATING MERCHANT POLICIES**  
Online merchants and others who participate in PriceSpider services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy. However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we cannot be responsible for their actions. We recommend that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.   
**ENFORCEMENT OF THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT**  
If you have questions regarding this statement, please contact PriceSpider at the postal and/or email addresses below.   
**CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT**  
We may occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "Updated" date at the top of this Privacy page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.   
**CONTACT INFORMATION**  
PriceSpider welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you believe that PriceSpider has not adhered to this privacy statement, please contact us electronically or via postal mail at the addresses provided below, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.   
**PriceSpider.com Privacy**  
8105 Irvine Center Drive  
Suite 1200  
Irvine, CA 92618
